1. openBrowser("")
5. navigateToUrl("https://fuse.staging.clearlink.com/#/")
9. setText(findTestObject("Page_Clearlink Authentication/input_to Fuse (Dev)_usr"), "frontpoint.qa@clearlink.com")
13. setEncryptedText(findTestObject("Page_Clearlink Authentication/input_Invalid username andor"), "h/wZhaWomj1SCqyUQOSQ/g==")
17. click(findTestObject("Page_Clearlink Authentication/button_Login"))
21. delay(3)
25. maximizeWindow()
29. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/a_FP"))
33. switchToWindowIndex("1")
37. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/input_First Name _customer_first_name"), "Test")
41. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/input_Last Name _customer_last_name"), "Person")
45. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/input_Phone _customer_phone_numbers_primary_phone_number"), "564-654-5645")
49. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/label_Yes"))
53. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/button_Next"))
57. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/input_Street Address _customer_addresses_primary_line1"), "1316 lavaca ct")
61. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/input_City _customer_addresses_primary_city"), "Cape Coral")
65. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/legend_StateProvince"))
69. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/div_City StateProvince AlabamaAlaskaArizona"))
73. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/input_ZipPostal Code _customer_addresses_primary_postal_code"), "33991")
77. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/input_Email _customer_email"), "test@testing.com")
81. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/input_Order Confirmation Number _order_confirmation_number"), "123456789")
85. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/div_Email Order Confirmation Number"))
89. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/i_Available Products_open-indicator"))
93. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/a_Safe Home Select"))
97. scrollToPosition(99, 99)
101. delay(2)
105. click(findTestObject("Frontpoint/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/button_Next"))
109. delay(2)
113. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/p_Collect and confirm name (spell back)"))
117. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/p_Collect and confirm the alternate contact n"))
121. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/p_Repeat and confirm monitoring package selected"))
125. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/p_Cover details on term monthly monitoring"))
129. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/p_Explain DIY process"))
133. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/p_Recap included equipment"))
137. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/p_Set shipping expectations"))
141. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/p_Cover date of first and future months payment date"))
145. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/p_Do I have permission to place this order"))
149. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/p_You also agree to enter into a"))
153. click(findTestObject("Frontpoint/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/span_Summary"))
157. delay(3)
161. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/button_Schedule"))