1. openBrowser("fuse.staging.clearlink.com")
5. setText(findTestObject("UAT login/Page_Clearlink Authentication/input_to Fuse (Dev)_usr"), "frontiersmb.qa@clearlink.com")
9. setText(findTestObject("REST examples/uatlogin1/Page_Clearlink Authentication/input_to Fuse (Dev)_pwd"), "Clink2019!")
13. click(findTestObject("REST examples/uatlogin1/Page_Clearlink Authentication/button_Login"))
17. maximizeWindow(STOP_ON_FAILURE)
21. delay(2)
25. click(findTestObject("Matts objects/FTRB customer slab/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/a_FTRB"))
29. delay(2)
33. switchToWindowIndex(1)
37. delay(2)
41. setText(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/input_First Name _customer_first_name"), "John")
45. setText(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/input_Last Name _customer_last_name"), "Scott")
49. setText(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/input_Email _customer_email"), "Miloiscool@testing.com")
53. setText(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/input_Phone _customer_phone_numbers_primary_phone_number"), "5645656587")
57. waitForElementClickable(findTestObject("vznmb customer page/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_Yes"), 0)
61. click(findTestObject("VZN phone consent/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_Yes"))
65. setText(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/input_Street Address _customer_addresses_primary_line1"), "1222 w athleen dr")
69. setText(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/input_City _customer_addresses_primary_city"), "West Jordan")
73. selectOptionByIndex(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/select_Alabama"), "45")
77. scrollToPosition(9999999, 9999999)
81. click(findTestObject("Matts objects/FTRB customer slab/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/span_Yes"))
85. setText(findTestObject("Matts objects/Ftrb customer/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/input_Business Name _order_business_name"), "Test company")
89. click(findTestObject("Matts objects/Ftrb customer/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/span_NA"))
93. click(findTestObject("Matts objects/FTRB customer slab/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/button_Next"))
97. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Matts objects/ftrb products/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/h1_Products"), 0)
101. setText(findTestObject("Matts objects/ftrb products/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/input_Frontier Order ID _frontierOrderID"), "321654987")
105. setText(findTestObject("Matts objects/ftrb products/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/input_Frontier Account Number _frontierAccountNumber"), "123456789")
109. setText(findTestObject("Matts objects/ftrb products/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/input_Installation Date _el-input__inner"), "07/10/2022")
113. selectOptionByIndex(findTestObject("Matts objects/ftrb products/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/select_8am-12pm9am-1pm10am-2pm11am-3pm12pm-4pm1pm-5pm"), 3)
117. click(findTestObject("Matts objects/ftrb products/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/input_Available Products_form-control"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
121. click(findTestObject("Matts objects/ftrb products/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/a_CTF Internet - FiOS 300300"))
125. delay(2)
129. click(findTestObject("Matts objects/ftrb products/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/button_Next"))
133. delay(3)
137. click(findTestObject("Matts objects/ftrb recaps 2/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/span_Collect and confirm customer Name"))
141. click(findTestObject("Matts objects/ftrb recaps 2/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/span_Repeat name of package package"))
145. click(findTestObject("Matts objects/ftrb recaps 2/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/span_Mention to the customer about Upfront"))
149. click(findTestObject("Matts objects/ftrb recaps 2/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/span_Read below Installation script for the"))
153. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Matts objects/ftrb recaps 2/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/span_Mention the Customer Service number- 1"), 0)
157. click(findTestObject("Matts objects/ftrb recaps 2/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/span_Mention the Customer Service number- 1"))
161. click(findTestObject("Matts objects/ftrb recaps 2/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/span_Read disclosure (NEW VERSION) for"))
165. click(findTestObject("Matts objects/ftrb recaps 2/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/span_Read below SMB Terms  Conditions"))
169. click(findTestObject("Matts objects/ftrb recaps 2/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/span_If FIOS is Sold play the Frontier FIOS Installation"))
173. click(findTestObject("Matts objects/ftrb recaps 2/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/span_Pitch Home Security to the customerPitch"))
177. scrollToPosition(9999999, 9999999)
181. click(findTestObject("Matts objects/ftrb recaps 2/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/button_Next"))
185. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Matts objects/ftrb summary page/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/a_Status Log"), 0)
189. scrollToPosition(9999999, 9999999)
193. click(findTestObject("Matts objects/ftrb summary page/Page_ Fuse (Frontiersmb qa)/button_Schedule"))
197. verifyTextPresent("scheduled", false, STOP_ON_FAILURE)