1. openBrowser("")
5. navigateToUrl("https://fuse.staging.clearlink.com/#/")
9. setText(findTestObject("Page_Clearlink Authentication/input_to Fuse (Dev)_usr"), "enercare.qa@clearlink.com")
13. setEncryptedText(findTestObject("Page_Clearlink Authentication/input_Invalid username andor"), "h/wZhaWomj2ebzjd4pfbrw==")
17. click(findTestObject("Page_Clearlink Authentication/button_Login"))
21. delay(3)
25. maximizeWindow()
29. click(findTestObject("All screen pop updated/Page_ Fuse all screen pop updated/Encr screen pop"))
33. switchToWindowIndex("1")
37. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/input_First Name _customer_first_name"), "Test")
41. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/input_Last Name _customer_last_name"), "Person")
45. click(findTestObject("Object Repository/Page_ Fuse (Frontpoint qa)/label_Yes"))
49. selectOptionByIndex(findTestObject("encr customer slab/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/select_Canada"), "0")
53. setText(findTestObject("encr customer slab/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/input_Street Address _customer_addresses_primary_line1"), "123 Drive rd")
57. setText(findTestObject("encr customer slab/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/input_Postal Code _customer_addresses_primary_postal_code"), "A1A1A1")
61. selectOptionByIndex(findTestObject("encr customer slab/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/select_AlbertaBritish ColumbiaManitoba"), 2)
65. setText(findTestObject("encr customer slab/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/input_City _customer_addresses_primary_city"), "Townsville")
69. click(findTestObject("Page_ Fuse (Scott Patterson)/label_Yes"), OPTIONAL)
73. setText(findTestObject("encr customer slab/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/input_Email _customer_email"), "test@mail.com")
77. scrollToPosition(9999999, 9999999)
81. click(findTestObject("encr customer slab/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/button_Next"))
85. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("encr springboard/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/h1_Springboard"), 0)
89. delay(3)
93. click(findTestObject("encr springboard/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/button_Next"))
97. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("encr products/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/h1_Products"), 0)
101. delay(1)
105. setText(findTestObject("encr products/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/input_Site ID _site_id"), "123654789")
109. click(findTestObject("encr products/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/span_CA"))
113. click(findTestObject("encr products/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/input_Available Products_form-control"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
117. click(findTestObject("encr products/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/a_HF05 - Furnace No heat"))
121. delay(1)
125. click(findTestObject("encr products/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/button_Next"))
129. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("encr recaps/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/h1_Recaps"), 0)
133. delay(1)
137. click(findTestObject("encr recaps/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/span_Confirm customers first name and last name (spell back)"))
141. click(findTestObject("encr recaps/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/span_Confirm customers phone number"))
145. click(findTestObject("encr recaps/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/span_Confirm customers physical Address and Billing Address"))
149. click(findTestObject("encr recaps/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/span_Confirm customers email address (spell back)"))
153. click(findTestObject("encr recaps/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/span_Confirmed other recaps present in DOK"))
157. click(findTestObject("encr recaps/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/button_Next"))
161. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("encr summary page/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/a_Status Log"), 0)
165. scrollToPosition(9999999, 9999999)
169. click(findTestObject("encr summary page/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/button_Schedule"))
173. waitForElementClickable(findTestObject("encr summary page/Page_ Fuse (Enercare qa)/a_Status Log"), 0)
177. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Matts objects/Encr schedule status"))