1. openBrowser("uatfuse.clearlink.com")
5. setText(findTestObject("UAT login/Page_Clearlink Authentication/input_to Fuse (Dev)_usr"), "verizonsmb.qa@clearlink.com")
9. setText(findTestObject("REST examples/uatlogin1/Page_Clearlink Authentication/input_to Fuse (Dev)_pwd"), "Clink2019")
13. click(findTestObject("REST examples/uatlogin1/Page_Clearlink Authentication/button_Login"))
17. maximizeWindow(STOP_ON_FAILURE)
21. delay(2)
25. click(findTestObject("All screen pop updated/Page_ Fuse all screen pop updated/a_VZNB"))
29. delay(2)
33. switchToWindowIndex(1)
37. delay(2)
41. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/input_First Name _customer_first_name"), OPTIONAL)
45. setText(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/input_First Name _customer_first_name"), "Changedagain4")
49. setText(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/input_Last Name _customer_last_name"), "Scott")
53. setText(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/input_Email _customer_email"), "Miloiscool@testing.com")
57. setText(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/input_Phone _customer_phone_numbers_primary_phone_number"), "5645656587")
61. delay(3)
65. click(findTestObject("VZN phone consent/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_Yes"))
69. setText(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/input_Street Address _customer_addresses_primary_line1"), "1222 w athleen dr")
73. setText(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/input_City _customer_addresses_primary_city"), "West Jordan")
77. selectOptionByIndex(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/select_Alabama"), "45")
81. setText(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/input_Business Name _customer_business_name"), "Milo is cool so let him buy the things you need")
85. delay(2)
89. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/button_Next"), 0)
93. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/button_Next"))
97. delay(2)
101. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_Products"))
105. setText(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/input_Verizon Order Number (MON) _order_brand_account_number"), "321654897")
109. setText(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/input_Installation Date _el-input__inner"), "06/18/2020")
113. selectOptionByIndex(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/select_8am-10am8am-12pm10am-12pm12pm-2pm12pm-4pm1pm-5pm"), 3)
117. delay(3)
121. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/input_Available Products_form-control"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
125. delay(2)
129. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/a_Bus Digital Voice Solutions Bundle MTM"))
133. delay(2)
137. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/button_Next"))
141. delay(7)
145. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_Collect and confirm customer Name (spell back) address primary Contact Number"))
149. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_Collect and confirm alternate contact number email (spell back) if customer has one"))
153. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_Business Digital Voice Only Advise the customer they will receive their equipment and a phone call 3 days prior to"))
157. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_Credit Check Statement Must Be Read"))
161. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_Life On FiOS - Do you have access to your email to go over your order with me"))
165. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_Discuss FiOS mobile access app when TV is sold"))
169. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_Customer Info (Collect Rebuttal Confirm) Customer Name Business name Address Primary Phone Alternate Email"))
173. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_Package Name Products Sold (Phone internet TV etc) Package Details (Speed long distance etc) Equipment"))
177. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_Monthly Recurring Pricing1st2nd Ye"))
181. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_Order Number and BTN (not guaranteed until date of installation)"))
185. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_Business Digital Voice Only Advise the customer they will receive their equipment and a phone call 3 days prior to"))
189. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_Business Digital Voice Only Verizon Business Digital"))
193. scrollToElement(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_First call resolution - I dont want you to have to call back so do you have any other questions for me"), 0)
197. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_Read Verbatim Only If LEC Phone Service Verizon wants you to know that you have a choice of"))
201. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_Read Verbatim on all Phone Setups The fulfillment information you receive will also contain"))
205. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_Read verbatim in Optix if set up MLB Extra Innings NHL Center Ice NFL Redzone etc"))
209. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_Read Verbatim if Collecting Card Information Please read me the name as it appears on the card"))
213. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_Provide wwwverizoncomwhatsnextbusiness to check order status"))
217. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_SMB Customer Service number 844-565-2532"))
221. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_Offer Referral Program (Encourage to fill out while on the phone)"))
225. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_Must get verbal permission to place order"))
229. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_Pitch Home Security"))
233. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_First call resolution - I dont want you to have to call back so do you have any other questions for me"))
237. delay(2)
241. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/span_Summary"))
245. delay(2)
249. click(findTestObject("Verizon SMB Object repo/Page_ Fuse (verizonsmb qa)/button_Schedule"))
253. closeBrowser()